Finding Aid for Gunnar Birkerts and Associates, 1960-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Federal Reserve Bank of Minneapolis, Minneapolis, Minnesota 1966-1989, 1676 drawings; 34 linear feet
  - Architectural Drawings
    - Project Drawings
      - Design Development Drawings
        - Drawings sent to F.R.S., Washington, and to Federal Reserve Bank of Minneapolis on December 9, 1968 (cont.). Blue-line prints, 10/25/1968
          - Mechanical Drawings by Jaros, Baum & Bolles, Consulting Mechanical & Electrical Engineers
            - Lobby-Mezzanine Level Plan (M-4, SK-M-20). 10/22/1968 revised, 10/25/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 29)
            - Stock Room and Mechanical Equipment Room Sections (M-5, SK-M-22 and 22A). 11/06/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 29)
            - Equipment Weights (M-6, SK-M-23). 11/26/1968 revised, 12/06/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 29)
            - Typical Tower Core Plans and Section(M-7, SK-M-25). 12/04/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 29)
            - Typical Tower Floor Reflected Ceiling Plan (M-8, SK-M-26). 12/9/68, revised 12/13/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 29)
            - Riser Diagram (M-9, SK-M-27). 12/13/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 29)
            - Drinking Fountain Detail (M-10, SK-P-1). 11/26/1968 revised, 12/13/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 29)
            - Typical Floor Plan, Preliminary (M-11, SK-P-2). 11/26/1968 revised, 12/13/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 29)
            - Plumbing Riser Diagrams, Preliminary (M-12, SK-P-4). 12/12/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 29)
            - Detail Sheet, Preliminary (M-13, SK-P-5). 11/26/1968 revised, 12/13/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 29)
            - Typical Tenth Floor and Eleventh Floor Plans, Preliminary (M-14, SK-P-6). 12/13/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 29)
            - Mechanical Equipment Room Floor and Roof Plans, Preliminary (M-15, SK-P-7). 12/13/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 29)
            - Passenger Elevator and Machine Room Plans and Sections, Preliminary (M-16, SK-EL-2). 11/11/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 29)
            - Passenger and Service Elevators Hoistway Details, Preliminary (M-17, SK-EL-3). 11/11/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 29)
            - Hydraulic Elevator Details, Preliminary (M-18, SK-EL-4). 11/11/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 29)
            - Parking Level Composite Lighting and Sprinklers (M-19, SK-ME-1). 12/13/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 29)
          - Electrical Drawings by Jaros, Baum & Bolles, Consulting Mechanical & Electrical Engineers
            - Header Duct Study, Second to Eleventh Floors (E-1, SK-E-5 and E-2, SK-E-6). Two prints 12/02/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 30)
            - Generator and Switchboard, UPS Battery and Equipment Rooms (E-3, SK-E-7). 12/11/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 30)
            - Core Lighting, Second to Eleventh Floors (E-4, SK-E-8). 12/12/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 30)
            - Light and Power Riser (E-5, SK-E-9). 12/13/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 30)
            - Emergency Riser Diagram (E-6, SK-E-10). 12/13/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 30)
        - Drawings Given to Knutson Construction Company on March 14, 1969
          - Structural Drawings by Skilling, Helle, Christiansen, Robertson, Consulting Structural Engineers. Blue-line prints, received 02/13/1969
            - Foundation and Parking Level (Lower) Plan (#11) (Map-case 10, Folder 31)
            - Foundation and Parking Level (Upper) Plan (#12) (Map-case 10, Folder 31)
            - Security Level (Lower) Plan (#13) (Map-case 10, Folder 31)
            - Security Level (Upper) Plan (#14) (Map-case 10, Folder 31)
            - Lobby-Mezzanine Level (Lower) Plan (#15) (Map-case 10, Folder 31)
            - Lobby-Mezzanine Level (Upper) Plan (#16) (Map-case 10, Folder 31)
            - Plaza Level (Lower) Plan (#17) (Map-case 10, Folder 31)
            - Plaza Level (Upper) Plan (#18) (Map-case 10, Folder 31)
            - Elevation of Wall Girder on Line "S" (#19) (Map-case 10, Folder 31)
            - Typical Floor Framing Plan (#20) (Map-case 10, Folder 31)
            - Mechanical Room Framing Plan (#21) (Map-case 10, Folder 31)
            - Roof Framing Plan (#22) (Map-case 10, Folder 31)
            - Tower Wall Elevation (#23) (Map-case 10, Folder 31)
            - Site Plan (#1) (Map-case 10, Folder 32)
            - Switch Gear Level Lighting and Utility Plan (#2) (Map-case 10, Folder 32)
            - Switch Gear Level Plan (#3) (Map-case 10, Folder 32)
            - Parking Level Lower Half Lighting Plan (#4) (Map-case 10, Folder 32)
            - Parking Level Upper Half Lighting Plan (#5) (Map-case 10, Folder 32)
            - Parking Level Lower Half Utility Plan (#6) (Map-case 10, Folder 32)
            - Parking Level Upper Half Utility Plan (#7) (Map-case 10, Folder 32)
            - Security Level Lower Half Lighting Plan (#8) (Map-case 10, Folder 32)
            - Security Level Upper Half Lighting Plan (#9) (Map-case 10, Folder 32)
            - Security Level Lower Half Utility Plan (#10) (Map-case 10, Folder 32)
            - Security Level Upper Half Utility Plan (#11) (Map-case 10, Folder 32)
            - Lobby-Mezzanine Level Lower Half Lighting Plan(#12) (Map-case 10, Folder 32)
            - Lobby-Mezzanine Level Upper Half Lighting Plan (#13) (Map-case 10, Folder 32)
            - Lobby-Mezzanine Level Lower Half Utility Plan (#14) (Map-case 10, Folder 32)
            - Lobby-Mezzanine Level Upper Half Utility Plan (#15) (Map-case 10, Folder 32)
            - Snow Melting Plan (#16) (Map-case 10, Folder 32)
          - Electrical Drawings by Jaros, Baum & Bolles, Consulting Mechanical & Electrical Engineers (cont.). Blue-line prints undated
            - Plaza Lighting at Three Plaza Levels (#17) (Map-case 10, Folder 33)
            - Second Through Eleventh Floor Plans (#18-27). Ten prints (Map-case 10, Folder 33)
            - Lightning Protection Plans and Sections (#28) (Map-case 10, Folder 33)
            - Kitchen Equipment Layout (#29) (Map-case 10, Folder 33)
            - Kitchen Schedules (#30) (Map-case 10, Folder 33)
            - Core Details (#31) (Map-case 10, Folder 33)
            - Telephone and Electric Closer Details (#32) (Map-case 10, Folder 33)
            - Power Riser (#33) (Map-case 10, Folder 33)
            - Emergency Riser (#34) (Map-case 10, Folder 33)
            - Stair and Exit Riser (#35) (Map-case 10, Folder 33)
            - Television and Sound System Risers (#36) (Map-case 10, Folder 33)
          - Mechanical and Plumbing Drawings by Jaros, Baum & Bolles, Consulting Mechanical & Electrical Engineers. Blue-line prints, undated, except as noted
            - Security Level Lower Half Plan (#37) (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Switch Gear Level Plan (#38) (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Eleventh Floor Plan (#39) (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Parking Level West Plan (#40, SK-M-103) (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Lobby-Mezzanine Level Upper Half Plan (#41, SK-M-107) (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Security Level Upper Half Plan (#42, SK-M-105) (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Lobby-Mezzanine Level East Plan (#43, SK-M-106) (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Tower Core Plans (#44) (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Detail Sheet No. 1 (#45, P-12) (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Roof and Twelfth Floor Mechanical Equipment Room Plans (#46, P-11) (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Eleventh and Third Through Tenth Floor Plans (#47, P-10) (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Second Floor Plan and Intermediate Levels (#48, P-9) (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Plaza Plan (#49, P-7) (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Lobby-Mezzanine Level Lower Half Plan (#50, P-6). 03/10/1969 (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Lobby-Mezzanine Level Upper Half Plan (#51, P-5). 03/10/1969 (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Security Level Lower Half Plan (#52, P-4). 03/10/1969 (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Security Level Upper Half Plan (#53, P-3). 03/10/1969 (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Parking Level Lower Half Plan (#54, P-2). 03/10/1969 (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
            - Parking Level Upper Half Plan (#55, P-1). 03/10/1969 (Map-case 10, Folder 34)
        - Plaza and Car Ramp Drawings
          - Tree Grate Plans and Sections by Neenah Foundry Company. Three pencil drawings on tracing paper and three blue-line prints with red ink notations 09/30/1968 (Map-case 10, Folder 35)
          - Planting Details. Blue-line print with red pencil notations 03/19/1969 (Map-case 10, Folder 35)
          - Miscellaneous Untitled Sketches. Five pencil and colored ink sketches on tracing paper undated (Map-case 10, Folder 35)
          - Typical Waterproofing System in Plaza Study Sketches. Five black and red ink drawings on tracing paper undated (Map-case 10, Folder 35)
          - Plaza Waterproofing and Structural Drawings (A8-1 to A8-4, ADD-460, ADD-481 and A3-8). Nine blue-line prints with consultants' notations in colored ink, three received 03/19/1969 (Map-case 10, Folder 35)
          - Typical Detail of Vertical Curve. Sepia print undated (Map-case 10, Folder 35)
          - [Miscellaneous Car Ramp Sketches], untitled. Two ink drawings on tracing paper undated (Map-case 10, Folder 35)
          - Layout of Car Ramp and Truck Ramp (A-DD-260). Four blue-line prints with consultants' notations in colored ink and pencil, received 11/68-1/69 (Map-case 10, Folder 35)
          - Car Ramp Curve Data (A-DD-340). Three blue-line prints with consultants' notations in colored ink, one received 1/69 (Map-case 10, Folder 35)
      - Construction Documents
        - First Drawings, Field Office Set, 4/23/69. Blue-line prints with pencil, ink and colored marker drawings and notations
          - Architectural Drawings with Area and Volume Calculations (A3-1 to A3-10; A4-1 to A4-6; and A5-3). Seventeen prints (Map-case 11, Folder 42)
        - First Drawings, Field Office Set 04/23/1969 (cont.). Blue-line prints with colored pencil notations, except as noted (Map-case 11, Folder 43)
          - Heating, Ventilating & Air Conditioning (HVAC-1 to HVAC-23). Six colored pencil and pen sketches on tracing paper and twenty-three prints (Map-case 11, Folder 43)
        - First Drawings, Field Office Set 04/23/1969 Blue-line prints with colored pencil notations
          - Plumbing Drawings (P-1 to P-16). Sixteen prints (Map-case 11, Folder 44)
          - Sprinkler System Drawings (SP-1 to SP-6). Six prints (Map-case 11, Folder 44)
          - Electrical Drawings (E-1 to E-29). Twenty-nine prints (Map-case 11, Folder 45)
          - Electrical Drawings (cont.) (E-30 to E-48). Nineteen prints (Map-case 11, Folder 46)
          - Elevator Drawings (EL-1 to EL-3). Three prints (Map-case 11, Folder 47)
          - Food Service Equipment Drawings (FS-1 to FS-4). Four prints (Map-case 11, Folder 47)
        - Drawings Issued for the Initial Substructure Contract Only on March 11, 1969. Bid set (office copy) of blue-line prints with notations in red pencil and ink
          - Site Plan (A1-1) (Map-case 12, Folder 48)
          - Site Plan, Existing Conditions (A1-2) by Harry S. Johnson Associates, Inc., Land Surveyors (Map-case 12, Folder 48)
          - Structural Drawings by Skilling, Helle, Christiansen, Robertson, Consulting Structural Engineers
            - Foundation Plan, East Side (S-1) (Map-case 12, Folder 48)
            - Foundation Plan, West Side (S-2) (Map-case 12, Folder 48)
            - Foundation Sections and Details (S-3) (Map-case 12, Folder 48)
            - Core Sections (S-4, S-41, S-42) (Map-case 12, Folder 48)
            - Elevator Core Sections (S-5, S-43) (Map-case 12, Folder 48)
            - Column Schedule and Details (S-6, S-35) (Map-case 12, Folder 48)
            - Typical Details (S-7, S-52) (Map-case 12, Folder 48)
        - Architectural Drawings. Pencil on linen drawings 06/19/1969, except as noted
          - Title Sheet (Map-case 12, Folder 49)
          - Site Plan (A1-1). Revised 05/19/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 49)
          - Site Plan-Existing Conditions (A1-2). Pencil notations on sepia print (Map-case 12, Folder 49)
          - Switchgear Room Level and Foundation Plan (A2-1) (Map-case 12, Folder 49)
          - Parking Level Plan (A2-2). Revised 03/31/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 49)
          - Security Level Plan (A2-3). Revised 03/31/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 49)
          - Lobby-Mezzanine Level Plan (A2-4). Revised 08/04/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 49)
          - Typical Tower Floor Plan (A2-5) (Map-case 12, Folder 49)
          - Switchgear Room Level Plan (A3-1) (Map-case 12, Folder 49)
          - Parking Level Plan (East Portion) (A3-2). Revised 04/07/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 49)
          - Parking Level Plan (West Portion) (A3-3). Revised 10/01/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 49)
          - Security Level Plan (East Portion) (A3-4). Revised 12/07/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 50)
          - Security Level Plan (West Portion) (A3-5). Revised 11/10/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 50)
          - Lobby-Mezzanine Level Plan (East Portion) (A3-6). Revised 12/07/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 50)
          - Lobby-Mezzanine Level Plan (West Portion) (A3-7). Revised 06/07/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 50)
          - Plaza Plan (East Portion) (A3-8). Revised 07/21/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 50)
          - Plaza Plan (West Portion) (A3-9). Revised 07/21/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 50)
          - Intermediate Landing Plan (A3-10). Revised 06/23/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 50)
          - Parking Level Reflected Ceiling Plan (East Portion) (A3-11). Revised 08/24/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 50)
          - Parking Level Reflected Ceiling Plan (West Portion) (A3-12). Revised 06/23/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 50)
          - Security Level Reflected Ceiling Plan (East Portion) (A3-13). Revised 05/01/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 50)
          - Security Level Reflected Ceiling Plan (West Portion) (A3-14). Revised 06/23/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 50)
          - Lobby-Mezzanine Level Reflected Ceiling Plan (East Portion) (A3-15). Revised 05/01/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 50)
          - Lobby-Mezzanine Level Reflected Ceiling Plan (West Portion) (A3-16). Revised 06/28/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 50)
          - Second and Third Floor Plans (A4-1). Revised 07/25/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 51)
          - Fourth and Fifth Floor Plans (A4-2). Revised 07/25/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 51)
          - Sixth and Seventh Floor Plans (A4-3). Revised 04/24/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 51)
          - Eighth and Ninth Floor Plans (A4-4). Revised 12/07/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 51)
          - Tenth and Eleventh Floor Plans (A4-5). Revised 04/18/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 51)
          - Mechanical Equipment Room Floor and Roof Plans (A4-6). Revised 06/16/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 51)
          - Plaza Level and Second to Eighth Floor Reflected Ceiling Plans (A4-7). Revised 05/01/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 51)
          - Ninth and Tenth Floor Reflected Ceiling Plans (A4-8). Revised 08/24/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 51)
          - Eleventh Floor Reflected Ceiling Plan (A4-9). Revised 12/30/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 51)
          - East Elevation (Marquette Avenue) (A5-1). Revised 07/21/1969 (Map-case 12, Folder 51)
          - South Elevation (Third Street) (A5-2). Revised 10/19/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 51)
          - West Elevation (Nicolett Avenue) (A5-3). Revised 10/19/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 52)
          - West Elevation (Nicolett Avenue) (A5-3). Pencil drawing on sepia print (Map-case 12, Folder 52)
          - North Elevation (Washington Avenue) (A5-4). Revised 04/22/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 52)
          - Sections (A6-1). Revised 04/05/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 52)
          - Sections (A6-2). Revised 09/03/1970 (Map-case 12, Folder 52)
          - Sections (A6-3). Revised 04/05/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 52)
          - Sections (A6-4). Revised 04/22/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 52)
          - Sections (A6-5). Revised 09/03/1970 (Map-case 12, Folder 52)
          - Sections (A6-6). Revised 04/05/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 52)
          - Sections (A6-7) (Map-case 12, Folder 52)
          - Sections (A6-8). Revised 06/23/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 52)
          - Sections (A6-9) Revised 10/15/1970 (Map-case 12, Folder 52)
          - Car and Truck Ramp Layout (A7-1). Revised 10/19/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 53)
          - Car and Truck Ramp Layout (A7-2) (Map-case 12, Folder 53)
          - Typical Tower Core Plans (A7-3). Revised 04/28/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 53)
          - Typical Tower Section (A7-4) (Map-case 12, Folder 53)
          - Stair #2 Section (A7-5). Revised 10/15/1970 (Map-case 12, Folder 53)
          - Stair #1 Section (A7-6). Revised 03/31/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 53)
          - North and South Penthouse Plans and Sections (A7-7). Revised 02/18/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 53)
          - Elevator Core Machine Room Plans and Sections (A7-8). Revised 04/28/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 53)
          - Elevator Core Sections (A7-9). Revised 04/28/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 53)
          - Plaza and Granite Details (A8-1). Revised 04/05/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 53)
          - Plaza and Granite Details (A8-2). Revised 09/03/1970 (Map-case 12, Folder 53)
          - Plaza and Granite Details (A8-3) (Map-case 12, Folder 53)
          - Plaza and Granite Details (A8-4). Revised 01/04/1970 (Map-case 12, Folder 53)
          - Plaza and Granite Details (A8-5). Revised 04/05/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 53)
          - Plaza and Granite Details (A8-6). Revised 07/21/1969 (Map-case 12, Folder 53)
          - Plaza Sculptured River Details (A8-7). 10/19/1971 revised, 05/19/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 54)
          - Window Wall and Metal Cladding Details (A9-1 to A9-5). Five drawings (Map-case 12, Folder 54)
          - Window Wall, Metal Cladding and Plaza Soffit Details (A9-6). Revised 06/23/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 54)
          - Window Wall and Metal Cladding Details (A-9-7) (Map-case 12, Folder 54)
          - Window Wall and Metal Cladding Details (A9-8 & A9-9). Two drawings, revised 04/28/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 54)
          - Window Wall and Metal Cladding Details (A9-10) (Map-case 12, Folder 54)
          - Window Wall and Metal Cladding Details (A9-11). Revised 09/17/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 54)
          - Window Wall and Metal Cladding Details (A9-12) (Map-case 12, Folder 54)
          - Window Wall and Metal Cladding Details (A9-13). Revised 04/28/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 54)
          - Typical Stair Details (A10-1). Revised 02/24/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 55)
          - Firing Range Details (A10-2). Revised 04/04/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 55)
          - Roof and Penthouse Details (A10-3). Revised 02/18/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 55)
          - Mechanical Equipment Room Details (A10-4). Revised 10/15/1970 (Map-case 12, Folder 55)
          - Mechanical Room and Penthouse Details (A10-5).Revised 11/02/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 55)
          - Typical Door Details (A11-1). Revised 06/28/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 55)
          - Granite Clad Door Details (A11-2). Revised 06/05/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 55)
          - Special Door Details (A11-3). Revised 04/22/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 55)
          - Special Door Details (A11-4). Revised 11/30/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 55)
          - Foyer Details (A12-1). Revised 05/23/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 55)
          - Lobby and Ceiling Details (A12-2). Revised 07/27/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 55)
          - Lobby Details-Elevations (A12-3). Revised 04/28/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 55)
          - Lobby and Wall Details (A12-4). Revised 04/28/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 55)
          - Vault Entrance and Adjacent Details (A12-5). 02/14/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 55)
          - Toilet and Locker Room Plans (A12-6). Revised 04/18/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 56)
          - Toilet and Locker Room Elevations and Details (A12-7). Revised 04/18/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 56)
          - Paying and Receiving Area Plan, Elevations and Details (A12-8). Revised 04/24/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 56)
          - Typical Demountable Partition Elevations and Details (A12-9). Revised 02/03/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 56)
          - Typical Wall Details (A12-10). Revised 11/09/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 56)
          - Security Court Elevations (A12-11). Revised 02/24/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 56)
          - Delivery Court Elevations (A12-12). Revised 02/24/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 56)
          - Delivery Court Elevations (A12-12). Pencil drawing on reverse sepia print, revised 02/24/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 56)
          - Security and Delivery Court Details (A12-13). Revised 04/22/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 56)
          - Security and Delivery Court and Guard Post #6 Details (A12-14). Revised 06/05/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 56)
          - Security and Delivery Court Dock Details (A12-15). Revised 11/12/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 56)
          - Guard Post 2, 3, 7 and 8 Details (A12-16). Revised 08/24/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 56)
          - Guard Post 2, 3, 7 and 8 Details (A12-17). Revised 06/05/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 56)
          - Parking Area Exhaust Shaft Details (A12-18) (Map-case 12, Folder 56)
          - Miscellaneous Details (A12-19). Revised 4/42 (Map-case 12, Folder 56)
          - Ninth Floor Plan, North Wing (A13-1). Revised 05/12/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Ninth Floor Plan, South Wing (A13-2). Revised 12/30/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Tenth Floor Plan, North Wing (A13-3). Revised 03/21/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Tenth Floor Plan, South Wing (A13-4). Revised 03/13/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Eleventh Floor Plan, North Wing (A13-5). Revised 03/21/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Eleventh Floor Plan, Kitchen and Dishwashing (A13-6). Revised 04/18/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Interior Elevations, Ninth Floor (A13-7). Revised 05/12/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Interior Elevations, Tenth Floor (A13-8). Revised 03/21/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Interior Elevations-Details, Tenth Floor (A13-9). 12/30/1971 revised, 03/21/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Interior Elevations, Eleventh Floor (A13-10). Revised 04/18/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Interior Elevations, Eleventh Floor (A13-11). Revised 03/21/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Wall Sections, Tower Floors (A13-12). Revised 05/12/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Vertical Details, Tower Floors (A13-13). Revised 03/21/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Plan Details, Tower Floors (A13-14). Revised 03/21/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Tower Core Details (A13-15). Revised 04/28/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Tower Ceiling Details (A13-16 & A13-17). Two drawings (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Cafeteria and Serving Line Details (A13-18). Revised 12/14/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Cafeteria and Serving Line Details (A13-19). Revised 03/28/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 57)
          - Miscellaneous Details (A14-1). 01/22/1971 revised, 06/07/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 58)
          - Miscellaneous Details (A14-2). Undated, revised 06/05/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 58)
          - Car Ramp Details (A14-3). 05/26/1971 revised, 08/24/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 58)
          - Miscellaneous Details (A14-4). 5/26/71 revised, 06/23/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 58)
          - Miscellaneous Details (A14-5). 5/26/71. revised 07/25/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 58)
          - Miscellaneous Details (A14-6). Pencil on velum drawing 05/21/1971 revised, 07/13/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 58)
          - Guard Consoles (A14-7). 7/9/71, revised 07/06/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 58)
          - Conveyor Details (A14-8). 6/8/71, revised 03/21/1972 (Map-case 12, Folder 58)
          - Revised Weldment Cladding (A14-9). Pencil on vellum drawing 07/28/1971 (Map-case 12, Folder 58)